rapidfa.net 2015-04-02

# Privacy Policy

You're here : Home __**Privacy Policy**

Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to us will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to contact as at yeye_chaley[at]yahoo.com.

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties**

OwnerGuide.net does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site.

**Browser information collected on the website**

OwnerGuide.net analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.

**Use of cookies**

OwnerGuide.net use cookies on this site

**Advertising Server**

OwnerGuide.net have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information.

**Respect to security**

OwnerGuide.net have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
